Wayne说你想见我
Wayne said you wanted to see me.
Keeler 他会在辩论中 提及你的前夫
Keeler. He's bringing your ex-husband into this debate,
证监会对他公司的调查
the SEC's investigation into his company.
Ted已被判有罪 并受到了法律制裁
Well, Ted was convicted and served his sentence, you know that.
Ted Packard想要的只是钱!
All that Ted Packard wants is money!
只要我们出钱 他们会在辩论前撤销陈述
If we pay him off he'll recant before this debate.
这是勒索!
It's blackmail!
凑够钱还来得及
We could have the money within the hour.
你不是和我爸在一起吗...
Thought you were with my dad...
你爸让我坐冷板凳 Kim
Your dad's side-lining me, Kim.
让他一边去!
Make him sit up!
我知道我爸很生我们的气 但他会消气的
Look, I know my dad can be hard but he will come around.
我们不应该告诉他
We shouldn't have told him.
还有一个办法 就是我们一刀两断
Well, the only other option I can think of is for us to stop seeing each other.
Chase 你怎么想?
Chase, what do you want?
我想做回自己的工作!
I want to be able to do my job!
Linda!
帮帮我!
I need your help!
如果交不出东西 这帮人会杀了我的
These guys, they will kill me if I don't get them something.
- 你在哪儿?  - 在商场
- Where are you?  - I'm at the mall.
反恐局知道毒品中没有病毒 他们正在抓Singer
CTU knows the powder's not real. Now they're going after Singer.
- 你要我怎么做?  - 抓住他 控制他
- What do you want me to do?  - Grab him and take him to containment.
是!
Done!
我们相信你儿子今早在墨西哥时
We believe your son was infected with a virus
感染上了一种病毒
in Mexico earlier this morning before he came home.
在他具有传染性前 我们有三小时时间找到他
We have three hours to find him before he becomes contagious.
找到了 Jack!
We got it, Jack!
他Los Feliz商场
He's at Los Feliz mall between Vermont and Sunset.
我十分钟后在那儿安插人手
I can land a team there in ten minutes.
很好
OK, fine.
- Kyle?  - 你是谁?
- Kyle?  - Who are you?
我是Tony Almeida 联邦探员 来帮你的
My name is Tony Almeida. I'm a federal agent but I'm here to help you.
- 我不相信你  - 跟我来 我证明给你看
- I don't believe you.  - Come with me, I'll prove it to you.
一名警官被击中了!
We have an officer down!
Kyle Singer逃了! 重复: Kyle Singer逃了
Kyle Singer's not in custody! I repeat: Kyle singer's not in custody!
医生! 请让一让!
Doctor! Get out of the way, please!
Jack没接电话 那里还有其它探员吗? Tony不是在那儿吗?
Jack isn't picking up. Aren't any other agents there? Isn't Tony there?
我也打不通他的电话 我试试Michael的
I can't get through to him either. I'm trying Michael right now.
怎么回事?
What's going on?
- 商场发生了枪击  - 什么时候?
- There's been gunshots at the mall.  - When?
两分钟前 我联系不上我爸和Tony
About two minutes ago. I can't get in touch with my dad, or Tony.
- Michael说有人被击中  - 谁?
- Michael said someone's down.  - Who?
Tony或Jack 不清楚 他马上去查
It's either Tony or Jack, he's not sure. He's about to find out.
稍等
Hold on.
是Jack 他想和你说话
It's Jack. He wants to talk to you.
- Jack出了什么事? Tony呢?  - 他中枪了
- Jack, what's going on? Where's Tony?  - He's been shot.
- 严重吗?  - 伤在颈部
- How bad?  - He was hit in the neck.
他还活着 已经送他去医院了
He's still alive. They're getting him into hospital now.
上帝啊!
Oh God!
Michelle 我知道你现在一定非常担忧
Michelle, I know how difficult this must be for you right now.
但你必须做决定
But you need to make a decision.
什么?
What?
Tony不在你就是总指挥 如果你想去医院陪他
With Tony down you're in command. If you wanna be by his side at the hospital
你要把工作移交给小组其它人
you're gonna have to hand CTU over to someone else.
没人会指责你这样做
No one will fault you for whatever you choose to do.
但如果你选择留下 就要全力以赴
But if you choose to stay, we need you to work at full capacity.
- 我明白  - Michelle 很抱歉
- I understand.  - Michelle, I'm sorry.
- Tony还好吗?  - 还不知道 他的颈部中了枪
- Is Tony all right?  - They don't know yet he was shot in the neck.
Michelle 我们的网络开始满负
Michelle, we're starting to overload the network.
病毒威胁出现时 我们启动了处理器的数据挪用周期
When the virus threat came in, we had start stealing cycles from the main CPE.
- Chloe 现在不是说这个的时候  - 什么? 你没疯吧?
- Chloe, now is not a good time.  - What are you talking about? Are you out of your mind?
你去处理 好吗?
Just deal with it, ok?
- Michelle?  - 卸载档案文件 存到另一个分区
- Michelle?  - Offload the archive files and send them to Division.
减轻网络负担
That should free up the network.
嗯 我想知道的就这么点儿!
Fine. That's all I needed to know!
我得去医院
I have to get to the hospital.
Michelle 快到会议室
Michelle, I need you in the conference area.
Hector Salazar的人打来了第二个电话
The second call from Hector Salazar's people just came in.
- 我现在没心情处理这些  - 那谁有?
- I am not in the position to deal with this right now.  - Who else is there?
你是这里最有资格的探员
You're the ranking agent on site.
Kim 查一下Tony在哪家医院
Kim, I want you to find out what hospital they took Tony to.
有任何关于他的消息 马上告诉我
The second anyone knows anything you have them patched through to me.
好
Ok.
把Ramon Salazar送到Bad Night车站 101高速公路附近
Deliver Ramon Salazar to the Bad Night Stand, adjacent to the 101 Freeway.
给他一个全波段的收音机
Provide him with a full spectrum band wave radio,
调到XQ2137频段 不许从空中或地面盯梢
adjusted to frequency XQ2137. Do not attempt aerial or ground surveillance.
收到电话后 你们有两小时来办理此事
You have two hours from the receipt of this message to comply.
如果违反条约 我们就散播病毒
If you violate any one of these conditions, we will release the virus.
和第一个电话的编码一致吗?
Does the encoding scheme match the first message?
一致
Yeah.
能找到它的来源吗?
Is there any way you can find out where it came from?
我扫描一下频率 也许能发现什么
I can scan the frequency, maybe we'll get lucky.
发这讯息给我们的人 控制着Kyle Singer的举动
Whoever sent this message is controling Kyle Singer's movements.
病毒散播前 我们有两小时去找到他
We have two hours to find him before they release the virus.
- Kyle?  - Linda 你在哪儿?
- Kyle?  - Linda, where are you?
我在找停车位 但有路障 好像发生了什么事
I'm trying to find a place to park but they're putting out some kind of barricades, something's going on here.
不 别去停车场 我们在东门出入口见?
No, no, don't go to the garage. Meet me outside the East entrance, ok?
Vermont街?
On Vermont?
对 对 我马上到
Yeah, yeah, go there now. I'll be there in a sec.
好吧!
Over here!
我找到他了!
I found him!
开车! 快!
Move over! Come on!
让开!
Get over!
- 出了什么事  - 我不知道
- What's going on?  - I don't know.
上哪儿?
Where are we going?
离开这儿
We just gotta get out of here.
这是即时通信器 如果发现了他
It's all contact frequency so if he shows up anywhere
立刻通知我们好吗?
please let me know as soon as possible, ok?
好
You got it.
抱歉
Excuse me.
- 怎么了?  - 我刚听说了Tony的事
- What's up?  - I just heard about Tony.
- 嗯  - 他怎样?
- Yeah.  - How's he doing?
正送往医院
He's on his way to the hospital.
- 为什么Michelle没去?  - 她知道 如果她和Tony都不在
- Why isn't Michelle with him?  - She knows it's gonna set us back
这边的工作就会跟不上进度
if she and Tony are both gone.
- 告诉Michell我要去监狱  - 你要去见Salazar?
- Tell Michell I'm heading over to Downey.  - You going to see Salazar?
对
Yeah.
我爸说审问他 是浪费时间
My dad said questioning him was a waste of time.
坐在这儿等才是浪费时间
No, sitting round in here is a waste of time.
你不觉得应该先跟Michelle说一声吗?
Don't you think you should clear it with Michelle first?
我们跟丢了那个感染病毒的孩子
We lost the kid who's infected with the virus.
- 只有Salazar才知道他的去向  - 至少走之前告诉她
- If anyone knows where he's going it's Salazar.  - At least run it by her before you go.
- 我到了监狱再打给她  - Chase!
- I'll call her from Downey.  - Chase!
我是Dessler
Dessler.
- 我找Tony Almeida的妻子  - 我正是 Michelle
- I'm looking for Tony Almeida's wife.  - Yes, this is Michelle.
Michelle 我是好人医院的Landser大夫
Michelle, this is Dr Landser at Good Samaritan hospital.
他怎样了?
How is he?
你丈夫颈上的伤 需要做血管修复
I'm afraid the wound to your husban's neck is gonna require some vascular repair.
我们要马上进行手术
We're just about to go into surgery.
能... 和他说说话吗?
Can... Can I talk to him?
不行 我们给他用了麻药
No, we've medicated him.
我们打来 是想得到你的口头同意
In fact that's why I'm calling you. We need your verbal consent to operate.
行 行 当然行... 一切听你们的...
Yes, yes, yes...Of course. Whatever you have to do...
- 很好谢谢  - 他会没事吧?
- Great, thanks.  - Are you sure he's gonna be ok?
还没手术 不能百分百保证 但我们用最好的医生
Well we can't say anything with a 100% certainty until we get in there. But he's gonna be in good hands.
手术结束请马上通知我
Please let me know the second you finish.
手术结束后 我到候诊室找你
I'll find you in the waiting room when we're out of surgery.
Landser大夫 我会尽量赶到 但...
Dr Landser, I will do my best to be there but...
你可能还是要用这个电话找我
you may have to reach me through this number.
好的 可以
Ok, we'll find you.
- 谢谢 大夫  - 不客气
- Thank you, Doctor.  - Sure.
我刚和Anne的前夫通过话 他半小时后过来
I just spoke with Anne's ex-husband. I'm meeting him in half an hour.
除非你改变主意...
Unless you're changing your mind...
我之前从未受过勒索
I've never given in to blackmail in my life.
是的 但想到今晚你会面临的一切...
Yes, but considering everything that you're up against today...
我们决定...
we decided that...
我决定付钱! 是我的选择
I decided to pay! It's my choice.
David 你选择是正确的
And David, you're making the right one.
给这小子钱 让他爬回窝里去
Give this guy some money, he crawls back under his rock
这样对大家都好
and life will be a lot simpler for everyone.
包括Anne
Including Anne.
但愿如此
I hope so.
喂
Yes.
Jack Bauer来电 阁下
I have Jack Bauer on the line, sir.
接过来
Put him through.
接通了总统 Bauer先生
The president's on the line, Mr Bauer.
总统阁下? 我是Jack Bauer
Mr President? It's Jack Bauer.
你好 Jack
Hello, Jack.
听说Hector Salazar给出了 释放他兄弟的细节要求
I was told that Hector Salazar has given your office final instructions on delivering his brother.
是的 阁下
Yes, sir.
还听说 你们能在此之前 先发制敌
I've also been told that you might be able to pre-empt that demand.
我们找到了病毒携带者 一个叫Kyle Singer的小伙子
We've identified the person carrying the virus. He is a young man named Kyle Singer.
- 找到他了吗?  - 没有 阁下 跟丢了
- Then you know where he is?  - No, sir. Unfortunately we lost him.
找得到他吗?
Can you find him?
在Hector Salazar给出的时间期限里 办不到
Not in the time-frame that Hector Salazar has given us to release his brother.
所以我只能交出Ramon Salazar 或承受病毒散播的危险
So, either I hand over Ramon Salazar or risk that his brother will release the virus.
总统阁下 我知道你不会这样选择
Mr President, I understand that this is an impossible choice.
这不是选择 Jack
It's not a choice, Jack. Not really.
不与恐怖分子协商 是对他们最有力的威慑 这是我国的政策
This nation's policy of non negotiation with terrorists has been a proven deterrent.
向Salazar妥协 会极大损害国家的政策
Capitulating to Salazar would effectively destroy that policy.
总统阁下 无数无辜的人可能会在一周内死去
Mr President, hundreds of thousands of innocent people may die within the week.
如果释放Salazar 今后会有更多人死去
More would die in the long run if I released Salazar.
我会将美国人民置于更危险的境地
I would be declaring open season on the American people.
- 这是你最后的答案?  - 我决不向恐怖分子妥协 Jack
- This is your final answer, sir?  - I don't negotiate with terrorists, Jack.
- 我不向恐怖分子妥协!  - 明白了 阁下
- I won't negotiate with terrorists!  - I understand Mr President, thank you.
召开疾防中心和卫生部会议
Conference in CDC and Health Services.
商讨全面检疫隔离和疏散计划
I want a full briefing on quarantine and evacuation procedures.
是 总统阁下
Yes, Mr President.
我们要去哪儿?
Can you just tell me where we're going?
不知道 就是离开这里 想出解决办法
I don't know, ok? I've just gotta get out of town for a second, and figure this whole thing out.
你不是要去见那些人吗 所以我才带钱过来
I thought you had to meet with those guys. That's why I brought you the money!
情况有变 好吗?
Things have changed, all right?
你在干嘛 Kyle? 你叫我偷爸爸的钱给你
What are you into, Kyle? I mean, you ask me to steal this money from my father
那些人就不会因你丢了毒品而伤害你...
so those guys won't hurt you over losing their drugs...
那可能不是毒品!
I don't think it was drugs!
什么? 那是什么?
What do you mean? What is it about?
不知道 今天警察去了我家
I don't know. These cops, they came to my apartment today,
他们说什么...
and they were saying something about...
利用我... 把病毒带到这个国家!
using me to... to bring some weird disease into the country!
病毒?
A disease?
嗯 警察说... 病毒在我身体里
Yeah. This cop, he was... he was saying it was inside of me.
你身体里?
In your body?
我知道...
I know...
听起来很可笑 是吗?
It sounds ridiculous, right?
是吗?
Right?
老天 事情太离奇了 对吗?
Man, this whole thing is so surreal, ain't it?
停车
Pull over.
什么?
What?
叫你停车!
I said pull over!
你干嘛? 你干嘛?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
车和钱都给你! 随便你 但别把我卷进去!
Take the car, take the money! Whatever you're doing, I don't want any part of it!
喂 linda! Linda 别这样! 别这样!
Hey look, linda! Linda, come on! Come on!
别靠近我 好吗? 如果你有病毒 我不想被传染!
Stay away from me, ok? If you've got some kind of disease, I don't want it!
- 谁叫你这么干的!  - 你以为我知道实情?
- You should have never done any of it!  - DON'T YOU THINK I KNOW THAT?
Kyle 别这样!
Kyle, please!
好 宝贝 你是对的 我不靠近你 好吗?
Fine, fine. Baby, you're right. You're right, I'll stay away, ok?
钱在前排座位下
The money's under the front seat.
别这样 Linda 求你了!
Ok, now, come on Linda, please!
Kyle 我真的不想你出事 但我帮不了你
Kyle, I really don't want anything to happen to you, ok? I really don't but I can't do this!
我真蠢!
How stupid am I!
对不起
I'm sorry.
快跑! 快跑! Linda! 快跑!
Go! Run! Run, Linda! Go!
阁下 我们做了隔离区的监控计划书
Sir, we have a monitoring plan for everyone inside the quarantine zone.
- 怎样的隔离区  - 起点处两英里范围的每个人
- Define the quarantine zone.  - Everyone within a two mile radius of ground zero,
起点就是Kyle Singer被发现的商场
ground zero being the shopping center where Kyle Singer was last seen.
总统阁下 我是卫生部的Nicole Duncan博士
Mr President, this is Dr Nicole Duncan at Health Services.
医疗队已就位 准备监测隔离区的人 72小时无恙后释放
Medical teams are in place and are ready to start screening and releasing people from quarantine over a 72 hour period.
如果行动迅速 我们能减少预估的受害者人数
If we move quickly, we believe we can lower the prior casualty estimate.
- 减到什么程序  - 六万至九万人之间
- Lower to what?  - Between 60000 and 90000.
我是Wayne Palmer 嗯... 嗯...
This is Wayne Palmer. Yeah...Yeah...
- 好 谢谢你们 Dessler女士 Duncan博士...  - 总统阁下
- All right, thank you, Miss Dessler, Dr Duncan...  - Mr President.
We're about to set into motion a chain of events that will create panick
可能会引起全国恐慌 要花时间才能控制
throughout the country, that will take some time to control.
在座有谁发现计划中的疏忽 请马上提出来
If anyone here sees an option that I'm overlooking, now's the time to offer it up.
Jack Bauer想和你单独谈谈 说是急事
It's Jack Bauer. He needs to talk to you in private, and he said it's urgent.
抱歉我离开一下?
Could you all excuse me for a moment?
现在请大家联系行动主要人员
In the meantime I want everyone to contact their key personnel,
确保他们做好了充分准备
make sure they're ready to go.
- 什么事 Jack?  - 总统阁下 这条电话线路可靠吗?
- What is it, Jack?  - Mr President, is this line secure?
可靠 你想说什么 Jack?
Yes. What do you need to tell me, Jack?
从价值观来说 我赞成
For what it's worth, sir, I agree with you supporting
不同恐怖分子谈判的国家政策...
this country's policy to not negotiate with terrorists...
Jack 你不会只想表达对我的赞同吧
Jack, you didn't call me to express your approval of my decision.
- 还有个选择你可参考  - 什么选择?
- I have another option for you to consider.  - Another option?
这个选择能保障国家政策的完整性 并防止恐怖事件暴发
Yes, one that, I believe, that will protect the integrity of this nation's policy and stop this outbreak from beginning.
- 我该怎么做?  - 什么都不做 阁下
- And how would I do this?  - By simply doing nothing, sir.
- 不做?  - 是的 阁下
- Nothing?  - Yes, Mr President.
可Hector Salazar会认为我们拒绝了他的要求
Hector Salazar will view that as non compliance with his demand.
看到他兄弟 他就不会那样想了
Not if he gets his brother back.
怎么做?
How?
找人将Ramon Salazar从监狱中救出来
Ramon Salazar would be broken out of prison and delivered to him.
公众 尤其是恐怖分子 会以为政府拒绝恐怖分子要求
The public and, more importantly, other terrorist groups would view this as a prison break
他只好自己逃狱了
as opposed to a capitulation to their terrorist demands.
听起来不错 Jack! 谁去把Salazar带出狱?
Sounds like quite a plan, Jack! Who breaks Salazar out?
- 我去  - 你去?
- I will, sir.  - By yourself?
我了解监狱布局 也有通行权
I know the prison and I have full access to the prisoner.
因为之前我和Salazars的瓜葛 我最有可能把他带出狱
Because of the nature of my involvement with the Salazars I can break him out and deliver him.
我在反恐局有不良记录 他们有理由相信我变节了
I have a history of insubordination with CTU, they would believe that I've switched sides.
- 我会做得很干净  - 这不像是一个人能完成的任务
- The cover story would stay clean.  - This doesn't sound like a one-man job.
为了保护您 只能一个人做
I think in order to protect you Mr President, this has to be.
我不知道 Jack
I don't know, Jack.
应该有别的办法
There has to be some other way.
不 不 剩下的时间可不多了
No, no. Not in the time that we've got left.
两小时后 Salazars会散播病毒
The Salazars are going to release the virus in the next two hours.
不管病毒爆发初期 你控制得多好
Regardless of how successful you are at containing the initial outbreak,
它引起的民众不安 会超过你预设的所有隔离区
the resulting civil unrest will far outreach any quarantine zones you've established.
这对国家来说 是毁灭性的破坏
The damage to this country, sir, would be catastrophic.
总统阁下?
Mr President?
我需要你授权
I need your "ok" on this.
即使你成功了 我也无法保护你免受法律制裁
Even if you succeed, I won't be able to protect your legal status.
你会成为流亡犯
You'll be a fugitive.
我明白 总统阁下 这是我最后的任务
I understand, Mr President. This will be my last assignment.
我不知该说什么
I don't know what to say.
如果你什么都不说 阁下 我视作你同意这次行动
If you don't say anything, Mr President, I will accept that as a "go" for this mission.
好运 总统阁下
Good luck, Mr President.
把Duncan博士的核心报告送到我办公室
I want the information from Dr Duncan's central records in my office.
只给我一个人
My eyes only.
Wayne?
- 你去哪儿?  - 抱歉
- Where are you going?  - Excuse me.
等等
Wait.
抱歉 Anne 我...
I'm sorry, Anne but I...
我有个约会
I have an appointment.
我快迟到了
And I am running late.
约会? 辩论会30分钟后开始!
An appointment? The debate starts in 30 minutes!
你去见谁?
Who are you meeting?
很抱歉 这是机密
I'm sorry again but that's confidential.
这是政府事务
It's government business.
和我前夫的事有关吗?
Does this have anything to do with my ex-husband?
我说了: 政府事务
Like I said: it's government business.
手术部 护士站
Surgery, nurses' station.
我是Tony Almeida的妻子Michelle 他的手术开始了吗?
Yes this is Tony Almeida's wife Michelle. I was wondering if he'd gone into surgery yet?
开始了
Yes he has.
我想告诉Landser大夫 他对青霉素过敏
I just wanted Dr Landser to know that he's allergic to penicillin.
他知道 你丈夫钱包里有过敏说明卡
Yes, he's aware of it. The allergy card was in his wallet.
现在能不能知道他的情况?
Is there a way to know how he's doing in there?
不行 大夫做完手术会联系你的
No but the doctor will contact you as soon as he's out of surgery.
好的 谢谢
Ok, thank you.
什么?
Yeah?
隔离区概图做好了
Er, the site profiles are done.
直接发到我系统就可以了
You could have sent these to my system.
我知道 但我想亲自送过来
Yeah, I know. I wanted to come down here anyway.
为什么?
Why?
因为刚才
Because of earlier.
刚才怎么了 Chloe?
What is it Chloe?
我想说 刚才我不知道Tony颈部中了枪
I just want you to know that I didn't know Tony had been shot in the neck,
所以态度有点不好 如果我知道
when I was insensitive earlier. And had I known
我说话就会注意一点 好吗?
I certainly would have been more careful about my choice of words, ok?
没事的 Chloe
It's fine Chloe.
我也会提醒别人注意的 好吗
I do try to be aware of other people, you know that, don't you?
我说了没事
I said it's fine.
好
Ok.
Gael?
干嘛?
What?
今天和Michelle说话要注意点 她现在很脆弱
I think we should be careful about how we talk to Michelle today. She's really sensitive.
因为Tony中枪了
About Tony being shot.
在颈部
In the neck.
当然
Of course.
我想提醒大家 让你部门的人也注意点
So I'm telling everybody. Make sure everyone in your department knows.
我接电话
I've got to take this call.
是私人电话吗?
Is this a personal cell?
不能接私人电话 因为无法监控
I thought those were prohibited because they can't be monitored?
有急事我才会用 我离开一会儿
I'm using it for an emergency, I'm moving around a lot.
有人会监控来电的 我得接电话
They'll monitor it at the other end. I've really got to take this call.
喂?
Hello?
什么时候打的第二次电话?
When did you make the second call?
20分钟前
20 minutes ago.
他们会放Ramon吗?
Are they letting Ramon go or no?
还没决定
They're still deciding.
你在等什么? 他们还有不到两小时!
What are they waiting for? They have less than two hours!
我得到消息会马上通知你
I'll let you know as soon as I hear anything.
对不起!
I'm sorry!
不是自己的东西 不许碰!
It's not good to touch what's not yours!
- 你姐知道你在这儿吗  - 不
- Does your sister know you're here?  - No.
这枪上了膛 知道吗?
Did you know it was loaded?
是把好枪 对吗?
It is a nice gun, huh?
拿着 Sergio 没事
Take it, Sergio, it's ok.
喜欢这感觉吗?
You like the way it feels? Huh?
想按下扳机吗?
You want to pull the trigger?
想听枪声吗?
Hear the noise it makes?
这就是这玩意儿的力量 Sergio
That's the power of these things, Sergio.
感觉像把枪!
It feels like a gun!
我能用?
Can I?
当然 来吧!
Sure. Sure. Come on!
看那个花瓶?
You see that vase down there?
瞄准它
Ok, now I want you to aim.
按紧扳机
And squeeze the trigger.
慢慢地
Very slowly.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
出去! 滚!
Get out of here! Go! Now!
说了多少次放过他 他还是个孩子!
How many times do I have to tell you to leave him alone? He's just a boy!
想变成男人的孩子!
A boy who needs to become a man!
你不是他爸爸!
You're not his father!
你想干嘛?
What you gonna do, huh?
朝我开枪?
You gonna shoot me?
来吧! 开枪! 朝这儿打!
Come on! Pull the trigger! Right here, come on!
进来!
Get in there!
你要对我们做什么?
What are you gonna do to us?
这... 这是什么?
What... What is this?
你们要做什么?
What are you gonna do to us?
来吧
Come.
我们还得再谈谈 你做了什么决定
We never really finished our conversation. I was just wondering what you had decided.
决定什么?
Decided about what?
辩论 如何对付我前夫
The debate. What to do about my ex-husband.
刚才我碰到Wayne 我知道他不喜欢我 但这次不同 他在躲避我...
I ran into Wayne a few minutes ago. I know he's never liked me but this was different. He was avoiding me and...
我有种感觉 让我无法动弹
I had a feeling I wasn't able to shake.
什么感觉?
What kind of feeling?
你付钱让Ted闭嘴! 我说得对吗 David?
That you're paying Ted to keep quiet! Is that what you're doing, David?
有时为了正确的理由 不得不做错误的事
Sometimes you have to do the wrong thing for the right reason.
怎么能付钱给一个撒谎的人? 这不对
How can you reward someone for threatening you with a lie? That's wrong.
如果我想留任 就必须考虑现实的政治问题
There are political realities I have to consider if I want to stay in office.
如果能让你感觉好点... 我告诉你...
I'll tell you something... If it makes you feel better...
不会让我感觉好! 这只是事实
It doesn't make me feel better! It just happens to be the truth.
Anne, I have been in this job for nearly four years.
And I have learnt the hard way that there are no absolutes. Sometimes you have to make compromises...
政治上是这样! 但如果和道德有关... David 你要明确界线
Politically, yes! But when it comes to morality... David, you have to draw the line.
我有界限 只是我俩在界限的两边!
I have drawn the line. We're just standing on different sides!
你让人感到害怕
You're running scared.
我努力留在办公室 为支持我的人民服务
I am fighting to stay in office and serve the people that put me here.
那就用事实迎战Keeler的谎言 相信人民能够明辨是非
Then face Keeler's lie with the truth and trust that the people will be able to tell the difference.
没那么容易!
It's not that easy!
你从没做过哪件事是容易的 你一直在做正确的事
You've never been about what's easy. You've been about what's right.
那才是你 人民选举那样的你领导大家
That's who you are. That's who the people elected to lead them.
那才是值得我爱的你
And for what it's worth, that's who I fell in love with.
我...
I was...
我是想保护你
I was trying to protect you.
保护我?
Protect me?
你不仅会受到Keeler的指责! 还要遭受媒体的检审
This won't end with Keeler's allegation! You're gonna be in the media's cross hairs.
我习惯于接受公众监审
I am used to public scrutiny.
这次不同 会比你想像的丑陋许多
Not like this! This will be different. And much uglier than you can imagine.
我会为自己辩护
I can defend myself.
David?
和Packard联系上了吗?
Have you made contact with Packard?
马上
Just going to.
和他在一起吗?
Are you with him now?
还没 他刚到 怎么了?
No, he's coming over now. Why?
离开那儿
Walk away.
什么?
What?
你听得很清楚
You heard me.
David 我们商量过 你打算掩盖这些事 记得吗?
David, we've been through this. Now, you decided to bury this thing, remember?
我改变主意了
I've changed my mind.
Anne和你谈过了?
Anne talked to you, didn't she?
Wayne! 离开那儿
Wayne! Walk away.
你找我?
You wanted to see me?
我找Chloe和Adam谈过 如果你想去医院陪Tony 我们来替你
I've spoken to Chloe, and Adam, and we'll cover for you if you want to go to the hospital to be with Tony.
替我?
Cover for me?
我们知道... 你脑子一定很乱
Well, we know... You've got a lot on your mind right now.
我没事 Gael!
I'm fine Gael!
我们觉得...
We just thought...
Michelle 危机出现后我处理了Chloe 30%的分析工作
Look, Michelle. I've been taking 30% of Chloe's load since the bio-threat came in.
我能处理一半的分析工作
I can handle half of COM's load as well.
我们只需要知道密码 免得在进入系统时浪费时间
We just need the right user password on district servers so we won't be slowed down by request authorization.
这是Joe Tommisello负责的 为了安全起见 他设置了用户延迟24小时权限
It's Joe Tommisello's area, he put a 24 hour delay on user logs because of security problems we've been having.
要不我打给Joe 让他开通权限?
So what if I call Joe and get him to wait for us?
我试过了 找不到他
I tried that, he's unreachable.
还有别的办法吗?
Is there any other way to do this?
增加人手 至少再要四个系统分析员来解密
More bodies. We need at least four more system radi-analysts to take on work we've been doing.
我打电话叫人过来 尽早开始工作
I can make some calls, get the next shift in early.
我试过了 等他们过来也迟了
I've already tried that. By the time they got here it would be too late.
我很感谢大家 但这办法行不通
Look, I appreciate this but it's not gonna happen.
都回去工作吧
So let's get back to work.
Michelle!
我同意 没有领导我们做不好工作
Listen, I agree. We can't run this place by committy.
让我接替你 Adam和Chloe做原来的工作
Let me step in for you. Adam and Chloe can stay at their posts.
你的工作怎么办?
What about yours?
我在Langley时 接替过当时的长官几次 干得不错
When I was at Langley, I filled out for my period chief a couple of times and we got through it.
当时有病毒威胁吗? 总统当天也在城市么?
Was there a bio-threat? President in town all in one day?
谢谢你 Gael
Thank you anyway, Gael.
反恐局 Bauer?
CTU, Bauer?
Kim 我是爸 你在干吗?
Kim, it's your dad, what are you doing right now?
还在分析Salazar手下来电的来源
I'm still trying to locate a point of origin on that phone call from Salazar's people.
听着 先帮我做点事 不会花多少时间
Ok, look, I'm gonna need you to do something for me first, it's not gonna take long.
- 什么事?  - 制作一份囚犯转移文件
- What?  - I need you to generate a prisoner transfer document.
注意文件格式 抬头写"联邦授权移交"
Look in your file form, under the heading "Federal Transit Authorization".
用来干嘛?
What's this about?
我要转移Ramon Salazar
I need to move Ramon Salazar.
为什么要转移他?
Why are you gonna move him?
Kim 这事得到了优先许可权
Kim, this has been given priority clearance.
反恐局其它人都不知道 所以我只信任你 让你帮我做
No-one in CTU's supposed to know. That's why you're the only person I can trust to do this for me.
快帮忙吧
So, please, help.
好的 要输入许可证密码
Ok. It's asking for a clearance code.
是*99
It's: *99.
还要一个进入密码
Now it wants a pass-word.
Lincoln 65 FGA.
Lincoln 65 FGA
可以了 要一分钟
Ok. It's cycling. It's gonna take a minute.
很好
Ok, good.
Kim 今早你到我办公室 告诉我一些对你很重要的事
Look, Kim, I know you tried to come up to my office earlier today to talk to me about something that was really important to you.
我不是很赞同 我只是...
And I know I wasn't very supportive and I just wanted to...
不用说这些 爸
You don't have to do this, dad.
宝贝 我要说 我想告诉你我很抱歉
Sweetheart, I do. I need to tell you I'm sorry.
我知道我对你保护过度
I know that I'm awfully protective of you.
近两年发生了太多事情... 我不想你再受伤害
I just watched so many things happen to you over the last few years... I don't want you to get hurt anymore.
其实 我相信你 相信你的眼光
The fact is, I trust you, I trust your jugement.
希望你明白 你的每一个选择 我都会支持
I need you to know that anything that you ever chose to do I would support you in.
好吗?
Ok?
谢谢 这些话对我很重要
Thanks that means a lot to me.
我很爱你 Kim
Good. I love you so much, Kim.
我也爱你 爸
I love you too, dad.
你没事吧?
Are you ok?
没事 文件做好了吗?
Yeah, yeah I'm all right. Is the document up yet?
嗯
Yeah.
马上发给Downey的典狱长Mitchell
Ok, I need you to send it to warden Mitchell, over at Downey, now.
发了
Done.
好 让我跟Chase说
Ok, good. Let me speak to Chase.
他不在这儿
He's not here.
什么? 他在哪儿?
What are you talking about? Where is he?
Kim? Chase在哪儿?
Kim? Kim, where is Chase?
他审问Salazar去了
He went to interrogate Salazar.
Chase现在在监狱?
Chase is at the prison, now?
15分钟前走的 快到了吧
He left about 15 minutes ago. He's gonna be there soon.
我再打给你
I'm gonna have to get back to you.
见鬼!
Son of a bitch!
喂
Yeah.
Chase 你在干嘛?
Chase, what are you doing?
去审问Salazar!
I'm gonna talk to Salazar!
马上回反恐局!
Get back to CTU now!
回去干嘛? 整理文档 打扫灰尘?
And do what? Some filing and some dusting round the office?
我要你和Michelle一起找出Kyle Singer!
No, I want you to work with Michelle and find Kyle Singer!
她让一群IT精英在做这事!
She's got a dozen IT people on that right now!
听我说!
Listen to me!
不! 你听我说 Jack
No! Listen to me, Jack.
我知道你生我和Kim的气 我理解 但你不能不让我工作!
I know you're angry about me and Kim, I get that! But I'm not gonna let you stop me from doing my job!
你的工作就是服从的我命令!
YOUR JOB IS TO FOLLOW MY ORDERS!
你无权命令我!
You're in no condition to give me orders!
Chase 我警告你 不许违抗我!
Chase, I'm warning you. Don't go against me!
Jack 你知道我尊敬你 你也知道我在为你隐瞒
Jack, look. You know I respect you but you also know I've been covering for you.
你回来后 我一直在为你保密
Since you've been back, I've been keeping the fact
不让Kim和大伙知道你染了毒瘾!
that you're a junkie from Kim and everybody else at CTU!
我不会再这样做了 我受够了
I'm not doing it anymore. I'm done.
Chase?
Chase? 见鬼!
Chase? Damn it!
让他按程序离开这里
Get this guy processed and get him out of here.
- Edmunds探员  - 典狱长 我要见Salazar
- Agent Edmunds.  - Warden. I need to see Salazar.
我现在很忙
I've got a lot going on right now.
我知道必须要有许可证 但你马上让我见Salazar
Have division follow up for written authorization but you need to let me see Salazar now.
Salazar买通了两个杀手 没有许可证谁也不许见他
Salazar's been buying two murders today. Nobody gets close to him without full paperwork.
你不明白今天发生了什么?
You don't understand what's happening today?
Salazar是我们的线索
Our Salazar has information that I need.
什么线索?
What kind of information?
机密!
It's classified!
这是我的部门 我必须知道
This is my facility. I need to know.
我们遭到恐怖威胁 Salazar的弟弟在幕后操纵
We're dealing with major terrorist threat. Salazar's brother is behind it.
尽管去跟总部审查许可证吧 几万条人命正危在旦夕
Go ahead and confirm with division if you want to. But hundreds of thousands of lives are at stake, here.
这三个月来 Jack和我一周来这儿两次
Now, Jack and I have been coming here twice a week for the last three months.
Salazar一直通过搪塞 律师 诉讼程序阻挠我们
Salazar's prevented us from doing our job with his stalling and his lawyers and his due process.
我们没时间浪费了...
We don't have time for that...
我要和他单独谈谈 马上
I need to go one on one with him, right now.
他在B区的隔离监狱 来吧 我带你去
He's in isolation cell in B block. Come on, I'll take you.
- 摄像头?  - 对 3个
- Surveillance cameras?  - Yeah, 3.
关掉它们
Get them turned off.
这不合规矩
It's against regulations.
我保证不会留下痕迹
Won't be any marks, I promise.
你有30分钟
You get 30 minutes.
我是典狱长Mitchell 关闭B区监视系统
This is warden Mitchell. I need you to go black on isolation B.
多久 先生?
For how long, sir?
到时候通知你
Until further notice.
你真是死缠烂打!
You're a tough guy, huh!
打我有什么后果 你不怕?
You are not worried of what might happen if you lay a finger on me?
好吧... 你不怕 我也不怕
Ok... If you're not worried, neither am I.
开始害怕跟我说一声
Let me know when you start to worry.
Kyle Singer在哪儿?
Where's Kyle Singer?
我说了 我不知道!
I told you, I don't know!
告诉我谁知道!
You're gonna tell me who does!
Chase!
让他回牢房
Put him in his cell.
你在这儿干嘛 Jack?
What are you doing here, Jack?
我们没有选择了
We're running out of options.
找不到Singer 现在Salazar是我们唯一线索 你是对的
We can't find Singer. Salazar's our only hope. You were right.
撬开他的嘴比想像的难 不如我们...
He's tougher to break than I thought. Maybe two of us can...
好
Yeah.
Jack 我刚才说的话...
Look, Jack, about what I said before...
- 忘掉吧  - 我们和好了?
- Forget about it.  - So we're ok? You and me?
对 和好了
Yeah, we're ok.
监视器在哪儿
Tell me about the security cameras.
关掉了
They're disabled.
很好
Good.
把他带出来
Get him out of his cell.
你要杀我吗 Jack?
Are you gonna kill me, now, Jack?
很想 但不能 如果你表现好 Ramon 我会带你出监狱
I'd love to, but I can't. If you play this cool, Ramon, you're walking out of here with me now.
几小时后 你就能见到你兄弟
You'll be with your brother in the next couple of hours.
拖他进去
Now, grab his feet.
面对墙壁
Turn and face the wall.
感觉怎么样 Anne...
How are you gonna feel, Anne...
如果David为了你输掉竞选?
if David loses this election because of you?
我认为不太可能
I don't think that's very likely.
你真不知道自己在说什么 是吗?
Mmm. Then you really don't know what you're talking about, do you?
这份陈述 会让他输掉这场辩论
Because this allegation may cost him this debate.
赢了辩论 才能赢选举
And David needs this debate to win this election.
这是勒索
It was blackmail.
David决定付钱了 你却让他改变了主意!
And David made the decision to pay. It wasn't up to you to change his mind!
如果他认为自己是对的 是不会改变主意的
If he believed the decision was right, he wouldn't have changed his mind.
问题是 你无法接受事实
The problem is, you can't stand the fact
你兄弟想和我过一辈子
that your brother wants me in his life.
因为你让他分心
Because you're a distraction to him.
你是个妨碍
And you're a liability.
跟谁比? Sherry?
Compared to whom? Sherry?
我不会在这儿为Sherry辩护 她是有点出轨
I'm not gonna sit here and try and defend Sherry. She went off the rails.
但至少她知道游戏规则 她了解David
But at least she understood the game, and she understood David. She was with him
他们在一起20多年
for over 20 years.
我和他一起的时间足够久 我了解他是什么人
I have been with him long enough to know the kind of man he is.
你根本不了解他
You don't know anything about him
或者你不了解这世界的生存法则
or what it takes to survive in the world he lives in.
我们有分歧 Wayne 一直如此
We disagree, Wayne. We always have.
Anne 我不会眼睁睁看着你毁掉他的事业
Anne, I will not stand by and watch you jeopardize everything that he's worked for.
我不会
I won't do it.
我不是那么容易被吓倒的
I don't scare easily.
怎么了 Jack? 自从你把我送进来 我不相信会你放我出去
What's happening, Jack? After all you went through to put me in here, I can't believe you're letting me out!
闭嘴
Shut up.
我不相信你叛变 你不是这样的人
I don't believe you sold out. It's not your nature.
为什么打晕那孩子? 你的政府屈服了但不承认? 是这样吗?
But then, why knock out the kid? Did your government cave, but can't admit it? Is that what happened?
你可没那么好 Jack 你是杂种!
You don't look so good, Jack. That's a bitch!
想出去吗? 那就闭上嘴照我说的做
You wanna get out of here? You'll keep your mouth shut and do what I say.
明白吗?
You understand me?
我们能通过了吗
We've been cleared to pass.
典狱长想见你 马上就到
The warden wants to see you first. He'll be here in a minute.
好
Ok.
不许动
Don't you move.
抱歉久等了 Jack
Sorry to keep you waiting, Jack.
什么事?
What's the problem?
这份转移令的密码
The access codes of this transfer order.
和监狱局签发的不一致
They don't correspond to the ones assigned by the bureau of prisons.
分区替换了这些密码 反恐小组有加前缀码的权利
Division superseded those access codes. CTU has a mandate to prefix.
这是昨天的前缀码
This is yesterday's prefix.
见鬼
Son of a bitch.
肯定是我办公室的人弄错了
Someone in my office must have screwed up.
我们马上把正确前缀码给你
Look, we'll get you the proper prefix retroactively.
听着 我知道恐怖威胁的事 Edmunds探员已经告诉我了
Look, I know about the terrorist threat. Agent Edmunds told me.
这就是为什么我们要转移犯人
That's exactly why we need to move the prisoner now.
这是最高机密 抱歉我不能告诉你
It's classified priority one, I'm sorry I couldn't tell you.
我不能为了繁琐的程序浪费任何时间
But I can't afford to lose any time over some small technical detail.
拜托 Kevin 帮个忙
Come on, Kevin, help me out.
Edmunds探员呢?
Where's agent Edmunds?
正在搜犯人的牢房 看能不能找到些线索
He's conducting a search of the prisoner's cell. Trying to find some additional information.
他跟着就出来 他会完成相关文件工作
He'll be right behind me, he can help you out with the paperwork.
好 带上你的徽章 准备通行
Right, pick up your badge and go to receiving.
谢谢 我们会尽快
Thanks, we'll hurry out.
走
Move.
请打开3号隔离牢房监视系统
Turn on isolation 3, please.
怎么回事?
What the hell?
有人动了摄像头 角度不对
Someone turned the camera, the angle's wrong.
让Binge到隔离区来见我
Get Binge to meet me in isolation.
开门
Door.
面对墙壁
Face the wall.
我是Bauer探员 能拿我的枪和徽章了吗?
Agent Bauer. Can I get my gun and a badge?
开门!
Open it!
Door!
今天好热!
Kind of hot today!
是啊 快烧着了!
Yeah, I'm burning!
不管Bauer说了什么 都是撒谎! 快!
Whatever Bauer told you, he's lying! Come on!
给 看看你的枪
Here you are, check your gun.
好
Ok.
Daniel 我来换岗
Daniel I'm back on post.
走!
Move!
3级警报 封锁全部牢房
Security 3, get a block of the whole ward.
解除封锁全部牢房 快!
Open the cell blocks, now!
在这儿没法解除
I can't do it from here.
你不怕没命吗?
Is it worth losing your life over?
快!
Do it now!
快! 快离开!
Come on! Get the hell out!